I tried shopping at Taemu for the first time this time
.  But let me
introduce you to some products that weren't as bad as I thought.
Taemu says that if you enter the coupon code now, you
can receive a bundle of coupons worth 390,000 won, so
get them right away.  This is a
random keyring.  I
would like to run Cinnamo here.  One, two,
three [scream] And just like that, true to my title as the King of Application, I have
picked a cinnamon.  This is a
Chinese keyring, and as those who watched the previous video
know, the quality and texture are
excellent.  And it's a random capybara figure
.  I bought this because it was so cute
.  I'll take a look.  [Laughs] I'm
Cafe Bara eating a banana.   Those of you who
know, you will recognize this: it
is Slang Beads.  I'll try making Slang
.
This is a mini smartphone decoration, is
n't it super cute?  The unexpected charm of this is that when
you turn it, cute anime characters are drawn on it, so I
think it would be great to use it as a decorative item.  This time, I
see a game character that was popular recently.
I bought this because I thought it would be good to hide it at my friend's house without them knowing.  Lastly, this is a figure
stand, so I’ll try placing a figure on it.   If you are a
serious figure enthusiast, you absolutely must
buy this.